key facts about pro-investor plus policy
pro-investor plus is a whole life
assurance policy with a savings and
investment component
it is ideal for clients seeking a return
on investment while guaranteeing
protection for their families in the
unfortunate event of death or disability
and critical illness
here are some key facts about
pro-investor plus that you may find
interesting
the pro-investor plus offers a life
cover during the investment cycle of the
policy when you save your investment
gives you a whole of life cover
irrespective of the premium paying term
the whole of life cover caters to death
critical illness and permanent total
disability
the policy gives you the option to
allocate any amount to the investment
component provided the risk cover is not
less than 20
what this means is that if you are
paying 300 000 every month a minimum of
twenty percent which is sixty thousand
goes to risk while you choose any
proportion to allocate to the investment
fund in this case two hundred and forty
thousand
this is provided the sum assured is not
less than 20 million
what are the benefits of the
pro-investor plus policy should you be
diagnosed with critical illness during
the premium paying time 30 of the death
benefit will be paid to you and your
policy will go through a premium waiver
this however does not change your death
or disability benefit
in the unfortunate event of death
prudential pays a hundred percent of the
sum assured plus occurred bonuses and
the available investment fund
in the event of permanent total
disability 100 of the sum assured up to
a maximum of 300 million is payable if
you become impaired
100 percent of the accumulated fund if
any will be paid to the policy holder
if you are between ages 18 and 65 speak
to a prudential financial advisor today
to get yourself a pro-investor plus
policy today
you can also call us on zero three one
two two five one four hundred what's up
zero seven zero seven triple four four
six seven
email us on customer care at
prudential.ug
life together today